pollenblog.com.au 2013-05-14

# Privacy policy - icon.pr

##  Privacy & Security Policy

##  Agreement

By choosing to use iconpr.com.au you agree to the following privacy terms.

##  Federal Principles

Our approach to privacy is guided by the Australian Government's National Privacy Principles <http://www.privacy.gov.au/publications/npps01.html>

##  Changes

We may change this Privacy Policy, or change, modify or withdraw access to this Site, or the content of these pages at any time with or without notice.

##  Collection Of Personal Information

We do not collect personal information on the sly. We only collect personal information that is necessary for the functioning of our site, and only with your consent. We only use lawful and fair means to do so, and not in an unreasonably intrusive way.

##  Disclosure

If our lawyers tell us to, we will hand over your personal details to the police. We will not use your personal information other than for the disclosed purpose unless we have reason to suspect that unlawful activity has been, is being or may be engaged in, and uses or discloses the personal information as a necessary part of its investigation of the matter or in reporting its concerns to relevant persons or authorities; or (a) the use or disclosure is required or authorised by or under law; or (b) we reasonably believe that the use or disclosure is reasonably necessary for one or more of the following by or on behalf of an enforcement body: (i) the prevention, detection, investigation, prosecution or punishment of criminal offences, breaches of a law imposing a penalty or sanction or breaches of a prescribed law; (ii) the enforcement of laws relating to the confiscation of the proceeds of crime; (iii) the protection of the public revenue; (iv) the prevention, detection, investigation or remedying of seriously improper conduct or prescribed conduct; (v) the preparation for, or conduct of, proceedings before any court or tribunal, or implementation of the orders of a court or tribunal.

##  Data Security

Securing your personal information is very important to us. iconpr.com.au will take reasonable steps to protect the personal information we hold from misuse and loss and from unauthorised access, modification or disclosure. iconpr.com.au will take reasonable steps to destroy or permanently de-identify personal information if it is no longer needed for any purpose for which the information may be used or disclosed.

##  Transborder Data Flows

Excluding legal requirements, we will not share your personal details without your permission. iconpr.com.au may transfer personal information about you to someone (other than iconpr.com.au or yourself) who is in a foreign country only if:(a) iconpr.com.au reasonably believes that the recipient of the information is subject to a law, binding scheme or contract which effectively upholds principles for fair handling of the information that are substantially similar to the National Privacy Principles; or (b) you consent to the transfer.

##  Sensitive Information

iconpr.com.au will not collect sensitive information about yourself unless:(a) you have consented; or(b) the collection is required by law or(c) the collection is necessary for the establishment, exercise or defence of a legal or equitable claim.

##  Liability

iconpr.com.au is not liable for any loss, liability, costs, expense or damage arising as a result of failing to meet any self-imposed standards.
